Guide to the New-York Historical Society Pictorial Archive 1804-2000 (bulk 1930-1960) NYHS 5
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series X. Architectural Plans and Drawings
  - H. B. Fishman & Co.: roof, gutter details, 1990 September 14 (Drawer 12A-9, Folder 4)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: roof and facade renovation plans, 1990 (Drawer 12A-9, Folder 5)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: floor plans, elevations, details, 1990 (Drawer 12A-9, Folder 6)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: existing and proposed plan and elevations, 1990 May 22 (Drawer 12A-9, Folder 7)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: store, elevators, corridor plans, 1990 July 24 (Drawer 12A-9, Folder 8)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: third floor renovations, 1990 (Drawer 12A-9, Folder 9)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: store - existing and proposed scheme, 1990 (Drawer 12A-9, Folder 10)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: facade, and roof elevations and plans, 1990 September (Drawer 12A-9, Folder 11)
  - Christina Weppner Designer: accounting and store management offices, 1990 June (Drawer 12A-9, Folder 12)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: floor plans, elevations, proposed and details, 1990 June (Drawer 12A-9, Folder 13)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: museum gift store plan and elevation, 1990 June 19 (Drawer 12A-9, Folder 14)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: gift store schemes, 1990 (Drawer 12A-9, Folder 15)
  - Richard Jansen Architect: proposed storage facility, 1990-1991 (Drawer 12A-9, Folder 16)
  - Allan Greenberg Architects: roof repair plan, 1990 (Drawer 12A-9, Folder 17)